Hey, I'm Liz Muller from Liz's Hair Design in Hollywood, Florida.
In this clip, we're going to discuss the best brand of hair color, permanent hair color.
I find that I've worked at, many lines in this industry.
Many different color lines, and one of the best permanent hair colors to me has been Framesi.
Framesi's been around since the seventies.
It's a wonderful product, and a for permanent hair color, they've come a long way.
They started out creme color, as a creme tube color with coconut oil, which is very rare.
You don't see that out there.
And they've introduced us to many other things in their line, but their permanent hair color is fabulous.
You can use their hair color on any type of hair.
I deal with ethnic hair and straight, Caucasian hair, and I tell you, I can use the line and really guarantee beautiful, long lasting hair color.
Gorgeous reds, beautiful reds that last a long time.
These are this permanent hair color.
This would be Futura right here.
They have a two-thousand and one line, called the Two-thousand and One line, color line.
But there's their gold colors right here.
Here's some of their coppery tones from Futura.
Just wonderful, the line of product.
And again, you'll find great results when you use Framesi hair color.
Thank you.
This has been Liz Muller.